{
    "subject": "resource/Carillon_Historical_Park",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:History_of_Dayton,_Ohio",
    "human_readable": "Carillon Historical Park is about History of Dayton, Ohio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9416552782058716,
            "question": "What is the significance of Carillon Historical Park for residents and visitors of Dayton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9312127828598022,
            "question": "What experiences does Carillon Historical Park offer related to Dayton's history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9156996011734009,
            "question": "Does Carillon Historical Park feature any artifacts from Dayton's past?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8841281533241272,
            "question": "How does Carillon Historical Park contribute to preserving Dayton's history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8594883680343628,
            "question": "What is Carillon Historical Park about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8450456261634827,
            "question": "Where is Carillon Historical Park located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7448287606239319,
            "question": "Who might find Carillon Historical Park interesting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7299972176551819,
            "question": "What kind of historical information can visitors learn at Carillon Historical Park?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6449479460716248,
            "question": "Are there any events or programs hosted at Carillon Historical Park related to history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5190438628196716,
            "question": "What aspect of Dayton, Ohio does the park focus on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carillon Historical Park is about History of Dayton, Ohio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2376_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any events or programs hosted at Carillon Historical Park related to history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2376_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of historical information can visitors learn at Carillon Historical Park?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2376_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might find Carillon Historical Park interesting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2376_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2376_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents mention \"Carillon Historical Park\" and its features, such as being a 65-acre open-air history museum, showcasing the stories of how Dayton changed the world, and having exhibits on technology and the evolution of Dayton.\n* The documents also mention Colonel Edward Deeds' vision for the park to be a museum complex filled with educational exhibits about the history of transportation and Dayton's contributions to world progress.\n\nBased on this information, I can conclude that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provided contain information that supports the statement \"Carillon Historical Park is about the history of Dayton, Ohio.\" Each document mentions various historical themes and exhibits related to the development and technological advancements in Dayton."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}